Happy Sunday. Welcome back to my
channel. If you're new here, hi. My name
is Alexia. I just got back from vacation
a couple of days ago already. And when
I'm away from home for a couple of days
or a couple of weeks, I just want to
dedicate a full day to do some
self-care, to do some cleaning, to
reset, to get back into my things. So,
that's what we're doing in today's
video. And I feel like it's been forever
since I filmed a Sunday reset. So, I'm
super happy to film this today. And
also, I know that it's been like a
couple of weeks that I haven't posted,
but I promise that I'm going to be
posting a lot more videos in the
upcoming weeks and months cuz I also
want to film like more days in my life
and just realistic uh days and just post
more vlogs on my channel and just being
more consistent. So, make sure you do
subscribe to my channel if you haven't
already to not miss any videos and also
give this video a little thumbs up. and
being away for I mean when I was on
vacation and being away from the cold
and this gloomy weather it honestly felt
amazing but now we're back into reality
and I also feel super grateful that I
get to get back to I mean to home and
just being in my things and knowing that
I'm just going to get back into routine
cuz I love being at home as well like I
love to escape and just being on
vacation obviously but I just love also
to be at home and be in my little
comfort zone as well. So yeah, anyways,
we are having a full Sunday reset,
Sunday self-care. And as I said, make
sure you are subscribed to my channel if
you haven't already. And let's get this
Sunday self-care reset started.
Hey
again.
It is time. It is time, you guys. While
the clothes are washing, I will need to
make another laundry after, but it is
time to deep clean, wash, and just
declutter my bathroom. I've been
procrastinating this so much. I think
the last time that I did this, it was
like maybe a year ago, which is insane
because I probably have a bunch of
expired products and I have bunch of
products that I don't use anymore. more.
There's a bunch of products just hanging
out on my vanity and I haven't touched
them in months. So, I need to do
something about this and it's truly a
disaster right now. You guys don't
really see anything, but my drawers are
a mess. So, take everything out, deep
clean. There's a lot of hair. If you're
a girl, you probably understand the fact
that we're always losing hair. So,
there's a lot of hair. And yeah, it's
probably going to take me a couple of
hours. But I think I'm going to put a
timer, like an hour and a half timer, I
think, or maybe 2 hours to do this
because this is always something that I
love to do cuz if I don't put a timer,
this like right here, everything that I
need to clean and declutter, I could do
this for an entire week if I don't put a
timer. So yeah, let's clean the
bathroom. Let's do this. And then we are
going to start another laundry. Also,
when you clean, make sure you're going
to put your favorite TV show or a vlog
or something. It helps so much to get
things done.
That's not even
Heat. Heat.
Hey.
Okay, so this is where I'm at right now.
So, I went through these two drawers and
they were all clean right now. I got rid
of so many products. It was actually
insane how many products I got rid of.
And here there's still a lot going on,
but I'm going to fix this right after. I
think right now I'm just going to make
myself something for breakfast and then
I'll be back to this. And over here we
have my vanity. I just know there's a
lot of makeup that is just way too old.
So, yeah, we're going to do this right
after. And I think I'm also going to
make myself a coffee to refill on this.
I made some scrambled eggs with some
onions and feta cheese. And I also made
a plain yogurt with chia seeds and also
some fruits and maple syrup. And I also
added a little bit of honey. Time to get
rid of some makeup products that are
probably expired or that I just don't
use anymore. Like this foundation is
probably 10 years old. I'm not even
kidding. So, yeah, I really need to go
through these jars and not keep things
uh just in case. I'm trying to be more
minimalist when it comes to my products
and makeup products this year so I don't
accumulate too much things for nothing.
So, so yeah, today we're getting rid of
the unnecessary energy. So, let's do it
for the makeup products now.
Hey,
hey, hey.
Hello. Hey. Hey.
So, the bathroom is all clean now. And
you guys are going to think I'm a clean
freak cuz I keep cleaning and
reorganizing everything in a lot of my
videos. But I hope this is going to give
you some motivation to get your life
together and to clean your space and
organize your things and just declutter
everything. But yeah, my bathroom was
something that I really needed to get
done. And now I'm going to put away some
clothes that are now clean. I still have
some laundry to finish cuz um I have a
lot of clothes from my trip. So I'm
going to organize my wardrobe now. And I
think after that I'm going to do like a
iPad reset and just prep for the week. I
also want to do like prepping my meals a
little bit, reset for the month cuz it
is now the month of February, which is
insane already. But I love this month so
much, especially because it's a pink
month. And yeah, I'm wearing the perfect
PJ for this occasion. It is the month of
February, the month of love, and I'm
actually so excited to have like a girly
month and everything about pink, I would
say. So, yeah, we're going to do a
little monthly reset right after
organizing my wardrobe.
Open.
So, I don't know about you guys, but I
really need a plan to function. And if I
don't know what's A and what's B and
what I need to get done by the end of
the week, forget it. I really need
structure. Taking time every Sunday to
plan my week can seriously change my
productivity. Doing this before it even
starts helps me so much to see
everything clearly like, okay, what's my
business plan for the week? What am I
looking forward to? And if you have a
super busy schedule as well, this really
helps you to see when you actually have
time for you, your workouts, your
friends, your family, or just your
hobbies and some activities that you
will like to do that week. So when the
week starts, you already feel more
grounded and in control. And I'm
actually doing this right now for the
next week. And it made me realize we
have been doing this for such a long
time since we were in school. And if
you're still in school, you probably
already do this. But we plan our study
days, our exams and everything. We used
to open our agendas and the teacher
would lay out the week and see what
we're doing on Tuesday and Friday and so
on. So I truly think that our minds work
better when we actually have a plan in
front of us. And if the plan needs to
change, that's totally fine as well. and
at least you know what to adjust and how
to move things around instead of just
feeling overwhelmed. And I'm also trying
to plan my meals a little bit more. Not
exactly what I'm going to eat every
single day for breakfast and for dinner
and everything, but just like getting
inspired. So, I love to like scroll on
Pinterest and save a bunch of images and
just see what recipes I can create that
week. So, I'm someone who um is having a
hard time just making sure I'm going to
eat my protein every single day, my
greens and everything. So, just browsing
a little bit has helped me so much. And
then I see if I'm missing some
ingredients and some foods for the week.
Well, I'm just going to go to the
grocery store for that. But just
planning my week, taking 30 minutes or
an hour every single Sunday. And
planning my week, my schedules, the
things that I need to get done, and just
my meals, as I said, has helped me so
much. And just staying on track. So, I'm
now going to go pick up a few things for
my meals of the week that I'm missing.
And I also want to bake some cookies
tonight cuz the new series of Bridgeten
is finally out. And I truly can't wait
cuz I've read the book. I mean, I've
read until Benedict story and I think it
was actually my favorite cuz it's
inspired, I think, by Cinderella, the
Cinderella story. So, I'm really excited
to see how good it is going to be. So, I
need to make this moment special. I
think I want to bake some Valentine's
Day cookies cuz it is that time of the
year. So, I always love to like
romanticize those moments, especially
when it's like a new movie or a new
series that I just can't wait to watch.
I love to like sit down, romanticize it,
bake, and eat some good food and all of
that. So yeah, that's what we're doing
tonight. We're having a full self-care
night. You guys know that these are my
favorites. And I think you guys also
love those type of videos. I mean,
self-care videos. So really excited to
go. So let's get going. I'm going to go
to the grocery store, as I said, just to
buy a few things that I'm missing.
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
So, here's everything I got at the
grocery store. And I got a lot of things
for my breakfast in the morning cuz I'm
trying not to skip my breakfast anymore.
But I got some lettuce. I love to make
myself some salads for lunch during the
week. I got two sweet potatoes cuz I'm
the only one who loves um them at home,
so I only got two. Then some cucumbers
for um my salads as well. Some eggs,
some bananas. These are for the recipe
that I'm going to make right now. My
spearmint tea. I needed to restock this.
You guys know this one is my favorite.
And then this tea that I also love when
I'm having a hard time falling asleep.
Here we have some popcorn and extra
butter cuz this one is just the best
one. I also got some fruits. So,
raspberries, strawberries, and
blueberries. I think strawberries is I
mean are always part of my grocery haul.
And then we have some bagels. And then I
also got this yogurt that I'm excited to
try cuz it's coconut flavor and there's
also no sugar and always lactoseree. And
then I also got my creamer for my
coffee. So yeah, that's everything I got
at the grocery store. And now I am going
to start making the cookies.
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
So, it's now time to do some self-care.
I'm going to put this face LED mask on
my face. I've been really consistent
with putting this on my face, I would
say, almost every single night when I
don't forget about it. And this is not
really the type of treatment that you're
going to see results like really
quickly. But one thing though that I saw
was the texture on my face. I think it's
a longterm treatment and I'm going to
see results probably in months. But if
you have been using this for months, let
me know if you saw a difference, if you
like it. And you have the red light and
also the blue light. I love to do both.
And the red light is good for wrinkles,
for um to boost collagen, also for acne
marks and inflammation. And then you
have the blue light which is good for
bacteras and also for acne. So that's
why I love to do both. I start with the
red light and then I switch to the blue
light and I do 15 minutes of each. So
yeah, it's kind of like my little
relaxing moment before bed. And it only
takes, as I said, 30 minutes. And I love
to like put something in the background
and listen to a podcast or just
meditate. It's just really relaxing. And
I always make sure to use a little
cotton pad with some misteller water and
just make sure it's clean cuz sometimes
there's dust that can be accumulated on
the mask. I'm going to show you like it
just it and it's it was a little bit
dirty. And I just do the same thing for
my face. I make sure my face is clean
always. And then after I always apply
like a really rich moisturizer cuz I
think the blue light can dry your face a
little bit. And I do have dry skin. So
always make sure to use um a really rich
moisturizer after, especially if you do
also have sensitive skin. It's also the
Super Bowl right now and I really can't
wait to watch Bud Bunny on TV. It's one
of my favorite artists. So I really
can't wait to watch the Alfime show, but
I also want to watch Bridgetton. I've
already watched like the first 15
minutes of the first episode, but I
think I'm just going to restart uh the
episode so I can just be really focused
and have my moment of watching
Bridgeten. And also let me know if you
are a Bridgeten fan, if you have watched
the show. I would say I think my
favorite season was season two, then it
was season 1. I mean, I really loved
season two and one. I can't really
choose which one is my favorite. I think
it was season 2 just because I think it
was a little bit more intense. But at
the same time, I really loved season 1.
I'm going to say season 2 first, then
season 1. And then season 3 was not
really my favorite, but I still enjoyed
it. But I think season 4 might be before
season 3. And we'll see if it's as good
as season 1 or season 2. I don't think
it's going to top season 2 cuz season 2
was really my favorite, honestly. It was
just so so good. So, anyways, I really
can't wait to watch season 4. First, I'm
going to do this face LED mask. And I
love to just close my eyes cuz my eyes
are kind of sensitive. So, the red light
is a little bit brighter, I would say.
But the blue light, it doesn't matter.
Sometimes I'm on my phone just watching
TV. But with the red light, I love to
close my eyes cuz, as I said, it's a
little bit brighter and my eyes are just
more sensitive to red light, I guess.
So, so I'm going to do the red light
now. And I am freezing right now for
some reason. And I'm going to put my
robe on. I'm always either in my PJs or
in a robe. I'm just a girl who is always
cold.
So, we just switched to the blue light
and now I can talk and see. And also, my
cat just joined me for this little
self-care moment. But if you guys didn't
know, I struggle with PIIE, which is
post-inflammatory arythemma. I finally
know how to say it, but basically, it's
a scar left by acne. And it is going to
fade with time, but sometimes it is
going to take forever. And it's so
annoying because when I have a pimple, I
know um there's going to be a scar after
and then I treat my scar, but then
there's another pimple and then another
scar. So, everything just happens all
over again and it repeats itself. So,
yeah, it's kind of annoying, but I guess
it's something that I hope I'm going to
be able to treat really soon cuz it's
been forever that I have this and I hope
this face deep face mask is going to
help. And there's also other ingredients
that I've been really loving and just
things that has helped me so much with
my acne. And I actually made a list on
my phone to tell you guys. So, first
thing that has helped me was to remove
any irritating product like exfoliating
too much. And I always use a gentle
cleanser. The one from Cetaphil is
honestly my favorite. I've been using
this for years now. And as I said, I
always make sure to use a really rich
moisturizer, especially if you do have
sensitive skin or dry skin during winter
as well. And then in the morning I
always make sure to use SPF because that
help for rosacea which I'm also
struggling with sometimes. And then when
it comes to ingredients the first one is
nioinamide. I've been also using this
for years now and it helps to fade my
scars. So I use it almost every single
night. And then there's also another one
which is kind of new I would say that
I've been adding into my routine for the
past months. It's Santella Aiatica and
that is good for inflammation to calm
irritation, red marks and all of that.
And I've been really loving this
ingredient. And then the other one is
also aelic acid which this is like maybe
stronger I would say. And you can and
also get the medical prescription if you
need like a stronger formula and I
actually have one and I really love it
as well. And then there's another
product that I bought recently which is
the medicube serum. So, I'm not sure
exactly what's the name, but I've got a
lot of question asking me if I loved
this serum. It's the Medicube PDRN Pink
Peptide Serum. And this serum is
supposed to help with your skin glow and
also for acne, acne marks and all of
that, but I would say that I'm not
really consistent with using this
product. So, I really need to use it
more and then give you guys my opinions.
But, um, I think I'm just going to
finish the bottle and then tell you guys
if I like it. So, yeah. I think it just
takes time and consistency when it comes
to the products that you use and also uh
some treatments that you decide to make
depending on your skin type. But for
now, I'm trusting on this face LED mask
and we'll see. I'm just going to wait
for it to finish. Then it's probably
going to be time to watch the halftime
show and then we're going to make some
tea and then we're going to watch
Bridgeten.
Are you